<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Exchange22 </string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="communicate">Communicate</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="sent">Sent</string>
    <string name="ravi_bhadani">Ravi Bhadani</string>
    <string name="ravibhadani_gmail_com">ravibhadani@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open"> Open navigation drawer </string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="message_fragment">Message Fragment</string>
    <string name="chat_fragment">Chat Fragment</string>
    <string name="profile_fragment">Profile Fragment</string>
    <string name="about">Exchange22 bring together India’s two favourite passion; sports and trading. The first of its’ kind sports fantasy league; Sports stock exchange.\n\nFounded in 2019, one of its kind sports fantasy concept, which merges sports and trading, along the lines of how a stock exchange operates. Instead of trading of stocks of companies, players’ are traded. \n\nWe believe that this one of a kind concept of sports fantasy league will redefine the fantasy league concept and set new benchmarks for its simple, user friendly interface and gameplay, letting the user enjoy and experience the game in a never before manner and even make money out of it. \n\nExchange22 is owned and operated by Hulm Entertainment Pvt. Ltd.</string>
    <string name="address_title">Noida, India</string>
    <string name="contact">+91 888-274-274-3</string>
    <string name="email_address">contact@exchange22.com</string>
    <string name="feature_1">No Team Creation.</string>
    <string name="featurer_2">Buy/Sell player(s).</string>
    <string name="feature_3">Buy/Sell as low as a single share.</string>
    <string name="feature_4">User Friendly Interface</string>
    <string name="feature__4">Create and Manage a Portfolio of player(s).</string>
    <string name="feature_6">Prices will fluctuate according to the performance in the live match.</string>
    <string name="feature_7">Instant results after every match.</string>
    <string name="feature_8">Simplified Points System.</string>
    <string name="feature_9">Attractive bonus offers for users.</string>
    <string name="play_description">Exchange22 is an unique gaming fantasy platform which provides the user with an unique concept of trading which allows the user to trade players.</string>
    <string name="step_one_title">Select a Match</string>
    <string name="step_one_Description">Select a match from the list of upcoming matches.</string>
    <string name="step_two_title">Create and Manage your Portfolio</string>
    <string name="step_two_Description">Create your own portfolio of players by selecting the player(s) based on your knowledge.</string>
    <string name="step_three">Monitor your Players</string>
    <string name="step_three_description">Once the game begins, check the players’ performance in the live match section.</string>
    <string name="step_four">Calculate your Points</string>
    <string name="step_four_Description">Scoring points depends on the Players’ performance. Calculate your points by referring to the Points Table.</string>
    <string name="step_five">Win Cash Prizes</string>
    <string name="step_five_description">Win real cash using your knowledge in sports</string>
    <string name="legality_one_title">Is it legal to play Exchange22?</string>
    <string name="ligality_two_title">So what exactly is a ‘game of skill’?</string>
    <string name="ligality_three_title">Which is the principal legislation governing gambling in India?</string>
    <string name="ligality_four_title">Is playing Fantasy Sports Legal in India?</string>
    <string name="ligality_five_title">Who are eligible to play Exchange22?</string>
    <string name="ligality_one_Description">Yes, Exchange22 is India’s first fantasy sport portal based on the model of a stock exchange and is a ‘game of skill’. The relevant law in India is absolutely clear that, unlike ‘games of chance’, games which substantially require a player to apply his skill are absolutely legal.</string>
    <string name="ligality_two_descripton">The principal legislation governing gambling in India is the Public Gambling Act, 1867 hereinafter referred to as “the Act”. The Act criminalises ‘gambling’ in a public forum and the keeping of a ‘common gaming house’. The Act, however, creates an important exception in favour of games of skill, by stating that the provisions of the Act shall not be held to apply to any ‘game of mere skill’ wherever played.</string>
    <string name="ligality_three_description">Fantasy Sports are not dependent on any outcome related to any real-life event and it is entirely based on the skillset of the participant(s) who uses their knowledge of the sport to determine the probable players likely to play in a certain match, a players’ forms, weather conditions and such other related factors. The result so achieved by a participant of a Fantasy Sports Game is entirely based on his/her skillset.\n\nThe Bombay High Court in the case of Gurdeep Singh Sachar v. Union of India relating to the legality of ‘Online Fantasy Sports Gaming’ offered by a certain fantasy sports platform has held that the games played on the fantasy platform were ‘games of skill’ and not ‘games of chance’. The court ruled that if the result of the game/contest is determined merely by chance or accident, any money put on stake with consciousness of risk and hope to gain, would be \'gambling\' or \'betting\'. Since that is not the case in fantasy games played on such platform, the same does not amount to gambling or betting.</string>
    <string name="ligality_five_Description">Exchange22 is strictly for users who are at least 18 years of age.\n\nCurrently, the residents of Assam, Odisha, Andhra Pradesh , Telangana, Nagaland, Sikkim and Tamil Nadu are not permitted to play pay-to-play formats of any online games. The laws in these states are unclear as to whether games of skill may be played for a cash prize.</string>
    <string name="ligality_four_description">Fantasy Sports are not dependent on any outcome related to any real-life event and it is entirely based on the skillset of the participant(s) who uses their knowledge of the sport to determine the probable players likely to play in a certain match, a players’ forms, weather conditions and such other related factors. The result so achieved by a participant of a Fantasy Sports Game is entirely based on his/her skillset.\n\nThe Bombay High Court in the case of Gurdeep Singh Sachar v. Union of India relating to the legality of ‘Online Fantasy Sports Gaming’ offered by a certain fantasy sports platform has held that the games played on the fantasy platform were ‘games of skill’ and not ‘games of chance’. The court ruled that if the result of the game/contest is determined merely by chance or accident, any money put on stake with consciousness of risk and hope to gain, would be \'gambling\' or \'betting\'. Since that is not the case in fantasy games played on such platform, the same does not amount to gambling or betting.</string>
    <string name="slogn">India’s First Sports \nStock Exchange</string>
    <string name="heading_line">Join Exchange22 and Experience the Thrill</string>
    <string name="privacy_heading">This privacy policy forms part of our “Portal’s” (hereinafter collectively refers to partner website(s) and mobile application(s))Terms and Conditions, by accepting the Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy on the registration page, any person utilizing the Portal, hereinafter referred to as the User or “you” or “your” or any of its features including participation in the various contests, games (including fantasy games, hereinafter referred to as Contest(s)Services being conducted on the Portal shall be bound by this Privacy Policy. You consent to provide Personal Information and are aware of the purpose of sharing such information. If you do not wish to consent to sharing of the mandatory personal information with Hulm Entertainment Private Limited hereinafter referred to as “Exchange22” or “we” or “us” or “our”, requested at the time of registration, request you to not to proceed with the registration. Registration procedure cannot be completed until information in the non-optional fields is provided\n        \n\nAt Exchange22, we aim to provide you with a safe, protected and reliable environment to play.We understand and respect your privacy and thus assure you that any Personal Information provided by you toExchange22 is protected and will be dealt with in accordance to this Policy. Exchange22 shall not provide, distribute, trade, sell or rent your name, e-mail address or other personal information provided on this site to any third party or information related to your usage of the Portal, except as provided in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacy_one_title">1. Information Gathered</string>
    <string name="privacy_one_Description">The information collected from you (the user) will be in the course of providing you with access to the Services and to the features offered through the Portal. \n\nUser\'s Personal Information includes the following types of Personal data or Information which has been categorised as under: \n\nSensitive Personal Data: \n\nWe do not normally collect Sensitive Personal Data except in accordance with or subject to this Privacy Policy. However, in certain circumstances, we may collect such information including but not limited to Financial information such as Bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details used by you to make any payments. We may also collect your PAN number details (as and when applicable). \n\nYou explicitly consent to provide such information as and when needed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and/or any agreement/contract entered into between Hulm Entertainment Private Limited and the User. Except for any financial information that you choose to provide while making payment for any Services on the Portal, Hulm Entertainment Private Limited does not collect any other Sensitive Personal Data in the course of providing the Services. \n\nFinancial information such as Bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details \n\nOther Personal Information: \n\nName \n\n Date of birth\n\n Contact number\n\n Postal/Contact address\n\n Account password\n\n The IP address of your computer, browser type and language.\n\n The date and the time during which you accessed the site.\n\n The address of the website which you may have used to link to the Website.\n\n Such other information that is defined as sensitive personal data or information in law. \n\nInformation from Social Media Platforms and Other Intermediaries: \n\nFurther, Exchange22 collects certain user information from social media platforms such as Facebook and intermediaries such as Google in order to help the users create an account on the Exchange22 Portal. The information collected by Exchange22 is stored in the database of Exchange22 and further displayed in the Profile section of the User in order to provide an identification of the User on the Exchange22 Portal. \n\n\t\tEmail Address:The email-id of the user using Facebook and Google services is collected by Exchange22 upon the user’s registration on the Portal using either of the social media platforms. The email-id collected by Exchange22 from such social media platforms is used to display in the user profile section of the User using Exchange22 services. \n\n\t\tName:Exchange22 also collects the name of the User who registers on Exchange22 through Facebook and Google. The name of the User to be displayed on the profile of the User so as validate the User as a verified user of Exchange22. \n\n\t\tDate of Birth:The Exchange22 Portal additionally collects the Date of Birth of the User when the individual upon registering on the Portal using either Facebook or Google. The Date of Birth collected is used by Exchange22 to authenticate the age of the User. \n\nYou shall be entitled to update the information provided by you by contacting us whichshall be updated subject to reasonable checks and confirmation by Exchange22. \n\nWe restrict access of personal information to our employees, contractors and agents and only allow access to those who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf.</string>
    <string name="privacy_two_title">2. Usage of the Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_two_description">All users of Exchange22 consent to the use of Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information for the purpose stated in this policy. Exchange22 may use the information gathered for the following purposes: \n\nFor the Purpose of Registration and to provide you access to the Services and features offered through the Portal and to verify your identity, Users would be required to provide certain information for the registration process namely: \n\n\t\t 1) Username \n\t\t 2) Password \n\t\t 3) Email address \n\t\t 4) Date of birth \n\t\t 4) PAN number (as applicable) \n\nIn certain instances, we may collect certain Sensitive Personal Data from you on the Portalsuch as information regarding the payment instrument/modes used by you to make such payments, which may include cardholder name, credit/debit card number (in encrypted form) with expiration date, banking details, wallet details etc. This information is presented to you at the time of making a payment to enable you to complete your payment expeditiously. Except for any financial information that you choose to provide while making payment for any Services on the Portal, Exchange22 does not collect any other Sensitive Personal Data in the course of providing the Services. Any Sensitive Personal Data collected by Exchange22 shall not be disclosed to any third party without your express consent, save as otherwise set out in this Privacy Policy or as provided in a separate written agreement between Exchange22 and you or as required by the applicable law. It is clarified that this condition shall not apply to publicly available information, including Sensitive Personal Data, in relation to you on the Portal. \n\n In the course of providing the Services, Users may invite other existing Users or other users hereinafter referred to as</string>
    <string name="privacy_three_title">3. Data Security</string>
    <string name="privacy_three_description">All the user information collected and stored by Exchange22 is the one which the user voluntarily submits. In addition, information submitted by the user is safely and securely stored within the Exchange22 database. The databases used by Exchange22 for storing the user information are protected by a firewall. The access to such servers is strictly limited and is password-protected in order to ensure a safe and secure storage of the user’s personal information. However, Exchange22 does not guarantee the security of the databases due to the fact that despite adopting various effective security measures, no security system is impenetrable or inaccessible. In addition to this, the user information can be obstructed amid the transfer of the information over the internet. Further, any sort of user information shared by the user amid the time of discussion over the site is public and can be easily accessed by anyone with Internet access. \n\n Exchange22 comprises of third-party advertisers that provide ads to the users at the time of their visit to Exchange22. These third-party advertisers might use the user information (excluding personal details like name, address, phone number etc.) for analysing and tracking the user visits to this and other websites, in order to understand the behavioural patterns or user interests, and then provide goods, services and other advertisements on the basis of user interests. Exchange22 shall not reveal, share or disclose the personal information or the identity of the user collected at the time of registration with these third-party advertisers. Several fraudulent emails, websites, blogs etc. often including the photos, logos, links, content or any other information associated with Exchange22, may, or are circulating on the Internet and claim to be from or associated with Exchange22. Such fraudulent emails, websites, blogs etc. might often ask the users to share their personal details including (but not limited to) like login name, password etc. In addition, these fraudulent websites, emails, blogs etc. might even demand the credit or debit card details of the user by convincing the users that they have won a prize or bonus amounts. Such emails, blogs, websites etc. are not associated with Exchange22 in any manner, and Exchange22 shall not be held responsible in an event any of the users reply to such emails or blogs or shares any information with them. Exchange22 strongly recommends the users not to trust, and respond to such mails, blogs, websites etc. and also not to share any credit /debit card details with them. \n\n Exchange22 may use your name, photo, Login ID and the state from where you are participating when announcing the results of any contests run on the Portal. Such contests are further governed by terms and conditions which shall be available on the Portals as and when such a contest is run on any Website. Exchange conducts periodic analysis and survey of the traffic to Exchange22.com for market research and advertising purposes. Exchange22 reserves the right to share your registration information with Exchange22 appointed market research and advertising companies or firms from time to time for the said purposes. \n\n Exchange22 also believes that the internet is an ever-evolving medium. We may periodically review from time to time and change our privacy policy to incorporate such future changes as may be considered appropriate, without any notice to you. Our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, how we store it and under what circumstances we disclose it. \n\n</string>
    <string name="privacy_four_title">4. Data Retention policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_four_description">Exchange22 shall retain the information provided by the users for such period of time as is required to fulfil the purposes for which such information is collected, as outlined in this Privacy Policy, subject to such longer time periods of retention as explicitly consented by the user or may be required under any applicable laws. We shall also undertake periodic review of Personal Information in order to determine whether it is necessary to retain the same.</string>
    <string name="privacy_five_title">5. Exemptions under this Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_five_description">Exchange22 may share any Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information without obtaining user consent, if sharing of such information is necessary: \n\n to comply with legal processes or governmental request;\n\n to enforce the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy \n\n :: Policy :: \n\n for prevention of fraud;\n\n for issues involving information security;\n\n to protect your rights, rights of Exchange22 and rights of \n\n the general public; and\n\n for such reasonable purposes (as may be prescribed by \n\n regulations governing the data protection framework in  India).</string>
    <string name="privacy_six_title">6. Limitation of Liability</string>
    <string name="privacy_six_description">Exchange22 confirms that this Privacy Policy is only a description of its operation regarding user information. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any legal rights in your favour or in the favour of any other person. Exchange22 reserves the right to change this Policy at any time without giving you prior notice. The liability of Exchange22 shall be limited to removal of Sensitive Personal Data from the system of the Portal and removal of personally identifiable elements of the Other Personal Information. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained in this Policy and elsewhere, the aggregate liability of Exchange22 for all claims for damages pursuant to provisions of services on the Portal, including claims in respect to the violation of this Policy, shall be limited to the aggregate maximum amount of liability as provided in the Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="privacy_seven_title">7. Contact Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_seven_description">Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy or any complaints, comments, concerns or feedback can be sent to Exchange22 at contact@exchange22.com.</string>
    <string name="splash_title">EXCHANGE22 GUIDE</string>
    <string name="term_one_title">1. Introduction</string>
    <string name="term_two_title">2. Legality</string>
    <string name="term_three_title">3. Intellectual property</string>
    <string name="term_four_title">4. Usage of Exchange22</string>
    <string name="term_five_title">5. Third Party Sites, Services and Products</string>
    <string name="term_six_title">6. Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="term_seven_title">7. User Representations</string>
    <string name="term_eight_title">8. User Registration</string>
    <string name="term_nine_title">9. User Account Operation</string>
    <string name="term_ten_title">10.. User Restrictions</string>
    <string name="term_ele_title">11. Technical glitches</string>
    <string name="term_trl_title">12. Withdrawal</string>
    <string name="term_thr_title">13. Disclaimers</string>
    <string name="term_one_description">These terms of conditions governs the rights between Hulm Entertainment Private Limited, its subsidiaries, affiliates, licensors, associates and partners, hereinafter referred to as The Company, we, us, our and such other adjectives and you (the user) hereinafter referred to as you, user, your, player, participants in relation to the use of products and/or services, hereinafter referred to as Services through its website www.exchange22.com and the Exchange22 App on both android and iOS devices, hereinafter collectively referred to as the Portal are all subject to and governed by these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, including any subsections in the Portal, hereinafter referred to as Terms. \n\nThe terms and conditions must be read by you (user) completely and well understood before agreeing to the said terms of usage, service governing any and all relationship with the products and services offered by the Portal. You understand that the Terms will be binding on you and agree that Services offered on the Portal can be accessed only in accordance with the Terms and it shall be your duty to comply with the Terms at all times. You are responsible to be aware of and agree to abide by the Terms as published and periodically amended or modified by Hulm Entertainment Private Limited.</string>
    <string name="term_two_description">Games of skill are legal as they are excluded from the ambit of Indian gambling legislations including the Public Gaming Act of 1867. The Indian Supreme Court in the cases of State of Andhra Pradesh v. K Satyanaryana (AIR 1968 SC 825) and KR Lakshmanan v. State of Tamil Nadu (AIR 1996 SC 1153) has held that a game in which success depends predominantly on the superior knowledge, attention, experience and adroitness of the player shall be classified as a game of skill. \n\nThe Content (across Exchange22) are games of skill as success of User(s) depends primarily on their superior knowledge of the game, knowledge of the players’ relative form, players’ performance across formats and conditions in fantasy games. By participating, each user acknowledges and agrees that he/she is participating in a game of skill.</string>
    <string name="term_three_description">Hulm Entertainment Private Limited hold all rights tangible or intangible for the Portal including (but not limited to) games, contests, advertisements, written content, photographs, graphics, images, illustrations, marks, logos, audio or video clippings, flash animation and all the services offered on the website including but not limited to all games and other content, promotional material, inter alia all strategic and development plans, ideas, designs, financial conditions, business plans, data banks, information related to technology and process, the technology developed including the software and methodology of usage, hereinafter collectively referred to as Intellectual Property.\n\nYou (the user) are granted a personal, non-exclusive, non-assignable and non-transferrable license to use the Content solely for the purposes of accessing and using the Services and for no other purposes whatsoever. The user shall not sublicense, assign or transfer the license granted, or shall rent / lease or any part of such license or of the Content included in such license. No transfer, copy, reproduction, distribution, exploitation, disassembling, translating, decoding, altering or make derivations from or make any other use of the Content on the Portal in any manner other than as permitted for obtaining Services on the Portal.\n\nNo right, title or interest in any downloaded materials or software is transferred to you by downloading and you are expressly prohibited from using such materials for any commercial purposes unless agreed with us in writing. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.</string>
    <string name="term_four_Description">Any person accessing the services or otherwise offered by Exchange22 on the Portal for the purpose of participating in trading of player(s) in any matches made available on the Exchange22 portal, hereinafter referred to as “Contest(s)” shall be bound by these Terms and Conditions, and all other rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services.\n\nExchange22 shall have all the rights to modify or change the already defined Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services at any point in time, by posting the same on Exchange22. Use of Exchange22 constitutes the User’s acceptance and agreement of such Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services, as amended from time to time. Exchange22 may, at its sole discretion, notify the User of any modification or amendment in these Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services by sending an email to the User\'s registered email address or posting notifications in the User accounts. In a circumstance wherein the User disagrees or does not accepts the amendments in the Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services, can use the options provided in such an email or notification to indicate their non-acceptance within a defined time frame. If a user fails to indicate his/ her non-acceptance of the amendments within the defined time period the User shall be deemed to have accepted the changes or modification in these Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services.\n\nCertain Exchange22 services offered by Exchange22 might be subjected to additional rules and regulations formulated in that respect. To that extent that these Terms and Conditions are inconsistent with the additional conditions formulated, the additional conditions shall prevail\n\nExchange22 may, at its sole and absolute discretion:\n\n\nRestrict, suspend, or terminate any User’s access to all or any part of Exchange22; \n\nChange, suspend, or discontinue all or any part of the Exchange22 Portal Services; \n\nDeactivate or delete a User’s account and all related information and files on the account; \n\nReject, move, or remove any material that may be submitted by a User; \n\nMove or remove any content that is available on Exchange22; \n\nEstablish general practices and limits concerning use of Exchange22 Portal; \n\nRevise or make additions to the roster of players available for selection in a Contest on account of revisions to the roster of players involved in the relevant Sports Event; and \n\nAssign its rights and liabilities to all User accounts hereunder to any entity (post intimation of such assignment shall be sent to all Users to their registered email ids). \n\nExchange22 holds all the rights to restrict, suspend or terminate a user’s access to all or any part of Exchange22 provided by Exchange22, deactivate or delete user account and information, delete user content without any prior notice to the user if any user is found or believed to be breaching the Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services illegally or inappropriately. Further, Exchange22 is authorized to take any technical or legal action against the user if deems necessary.\n\ntext In the event of suspension or deletion of a user\'s account due to negligence on the part of Exchange22, then, the company shall repay the fee charged for any of the Services provided by Exchange22, without any delay. However, no refund would be made in case of suspension or removal due to any breach of the Terms and Conditions, rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services or inappropriate use of Exchange22; or any circumstances beyond the reasonable control of Exchange22. \n\nThe users consent to receive communications including announcements, administrative messages, and advertisements from Exchange22 or any of its partners, licensors or associates.</string>
    <string name="term_five_description">Exchange22 Portal may contain information about or hyperlinks to third parties. In such cases, Exchange22 shall not be held responsible in any manner and do not extend any express or implied warranty to the accuracy, integrity or quality of the content belonging to such third party websites or apps or for any content posted on any third-party Internet site. Further, the involvement of Exchange22 with any of the third-party content or links to third-party Internet sites is not related to any sort of endorsement by Exchange22 of such third-party Internet site. If you rely on any third party Content posted on any website or app which does not belong to Exchange22, you may do so solely at your own risk and liability.\n\nExchange22 is neither associated with nor responsible for the correspondence, transactions, and all other related activities between the user and third parties including payment gateway providers and verification service providers on Exchange22. The users\' involvement with third parties is entirely dependent on the terms and conditions, policies and services terms of these third parties and the users are solely responsible for reviewing the policies, terms and conditions, and the service terms of these third parties before transacting or availing any of the services. Accepting the Terms and Conditions of Exchange22 the users agree that Exchange22 is not responsible for any sort of damage or loss faced by the users due to any sort of transactions, correspondence and all related activities with any of the third parties. Any questions, complaints, or claims related to any third party product or service should be directed to the appropriate vendor.</string>
    <string name="term_six_description">All information collected from users, such as registration and payment information, is subject to Exchange22’s Privacy Policy which is available at Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="term_seven_description">Any information provided by you (the User) to us, whether at the stage of registration or during anytime subsequently, should be authentic.\n\nPrior to adding cash to your user account or participating in Contest(s), the responsibility to satisfy the legality of such Contest(s) in the jurisdiction from where you are accessing the Contest(s) shall be on you. If you are not legally competent to individually enter into Indian Rupee transactions through banking channels in India and/or are not accessing any Portal from a permitted jurisdiction, you are prohibited from participating in Contest(s) on the Portal. In the event of such violation, your participation in Contest(s) will be deemed to be in breach of the Terms and you will not be entitled to receive any prize that you might win in such Contest(s).\n\n You represent that you are 18 years of age or older to participate in any Contest(s) and are also otherwise competent to enter into transactions with other users and us. You are aware that participation in the Contest(s) organized by us, hereinafter referred to as \'Activity\' may result in financial loss to you. With full knowledge of the facts and circumstances surrounding this Activity, you are voluntarily participating in the Activity and assume all responsibility and risk resulting from your participation, including all risk of financial loss. You agree to indemnify and hold us, our employees, directors, officers, and agents harmless with respect to any and all claims and costs associated with your participation in the Activity.\n\n You represent that you have the experience and the requisite skills and knowledge required to participate in the Activity and that you are not aware of any physical or mental condition that would impair your capability to fully participate in the Activity. You further acknowledge that you are solely responsible for any consequence resulting from you participating in this Activity or being associated with this Activity or around this Activity. You understand that we assume no liability or responsibility for any financial loss that you may sustain as a result of your participation in the Activity.\n\n You understand and accept that your participation in a Contest available on the Portal does not create any obligation on us to give you any winnings. Your winnings are entirely dependent on your skill as a player vis-a-vis other players in the Contest and subject to the rules of the Contest.\n\n You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for all content posted, transmitted, uploaded or otherwise made available on the Portal by you. All content posted by you must be legally owned by or licensed to you. By publishing any content on the Website, you agree to grant us a royalty-free, world-wide, non- exclusive, perpetual and assignable right to use, copy, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, edit, translate, create derivative works from, transmit, distribute, publicly display, and publicly perform your content and to use such content in any related marketing materials produced by us or our affiliates. Such content may include, without limitation, your name, username, location, messages, gender or pictures. You also understand that you do not obtain any rights, legal or equitable, in any material incorporating your content. You further agree and acknowledge that we have the right to use in any manner whatsoever, all communication or feedback provided by you.\n\n You understand and accept that we reserve the right to record any and all user content produced by way of but not limited to chat messages on the Portal through our feature, through the in-game chat facility or other interactive features, if any, offered as part of the Services.\n\n You shall not hold us responsible for not being able to play any Contest(s) for which you may be eligible to participate. This includes but is not limited to situations where you are unable to log into your user account as your user account may be pending validation or you may be suspected or established violation of any of the Terms.\n\n You understand and accept that by viewing or using the Portal or availing of any Services, or using communication features on the Portal, you may be exposed to content posted by other users which you may find offensive, objectionable or indecent. You may bring such content posted by other users to our notice that you may find offensive, objectionable or indecent and we reserve the right to act upon it as we may deem fit. The decision taken by us on this regard shall be final and binding on you.</string>
    <string name="term_eight_description"><![CDATA[In order to register for the Contest(s), User(s) are required to provide the following information accurately:\n\n \t\tFull Name \n\t\tE-mail Address \n\t\tPassword \n\t\tComplete Address \n\t\tGender \n\t\tDate of Birth \n\nThe Full Name and Date of Birth mentioned by the User for the purpose of verification should match with the Name and Date of Birth mentioned on all the documents required to be uploaded for verification purposes. \n\n The User participating in activities, services or features provided by Exchange22 are required to provide their approval stating they have carefully read all the terms and conditions and will comply with all the rules, regulations, and terms of use referred to herein or provided by Exchange22 in relation to Exchange22 services.\n\n The User(s) entering any contest(s) organized by Exchange22 as a resident of Sikkim, Assam, Odisha, Telangana, Nagaland, Andhra Pradesh and Tamil Nadu will not be permitted to sign up for any round in the paid version of the Contest as elaborated below. In case of audits from Exchange22, if a user is found to be a resident of Sikkim, Assam, Odisha, Telangana or Nagaland, Andhra Pradesh and Tamil Nadu but not stated at the time of registration then Exchange22 at its sole and absolute discretion holds the rights to take action against such user including (but not limited to) blocking of user account, deletion or deactivation of user account, and resetting the user account to initial level by deleting all the logs, refers & reducing the amount present in the user wallet to “zero”. In an event, the state laws of these states change and the residents of these states are allowed to participate in the paid versions of Game of Skills, the users (which were blocked earlier for being a resident of these states) shall be treated as new registrations and in no case previous winnings shall be considered and any claim of such sort will not be entertained in any case.\n\n The User(s) who are only above the age of 18 years and have successfully completed their registration process by entering valid and adequate information in the registration form are sent a confirmation email comprising their login details.\nOnly those User(s) who have successfully registered on the Exchange22 App as well as registered prior to each round in accordance with the procedure outlined above shall be eligible to participate in the Contest(s) and win.\n\n \n\nIn case of PAN card verification, it is mandatory to upload a full image of the original PAN card. No scanned image of a photocopy of the users’ PAN card will be acceptable for verification purposes. \n\nIn case, you are uploading an E-PAN card for PAN card verification process then it is mandatory to upload a full scanned image of the E-PAN card (both front and back).\n\n Exchange22 reserves the right to disallow you from logging into the Portal or reduce your play limits until we are able to satisfactorily validate your user account. Exchange22 will in such events email you to notify you of the next steps regarding user account validation. We may also ask you for proof of identification and proof of address from time to time.\n\n Upon receipt of suitable documents, we will try our best to enable your user account at the earliest. However, it may take a few business days to reinstate your user account.\n\n In the event the address provided by you is incorrect, Exchange22 will not make any additional attempts for delivery of the cheque unless a correct address is provided by you and charges for redelivery as prescribed by us are paid by you.\n\n The Privacy Policy of our Portal forms a part of the Terms. All personal information which is of such nature that requires protection from unauthorized dissemination shall be dealt with in the manner provided in the Privacy Policy of the Portal.]]></string>
    <string name="term_nine_Description"><![CDATA[By accepting the Terms and Conditions of Exchange22, the User using Services provided by Exchange22 agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information while registration and at other times when demanded by Exchange22. The User further provides consent to keeping his/her registration information updated at all times. \n\n A single user is permitted to register or operate only one user account with Exchange22 Portal (inclusive of both web & app).\n\nThe User using the services provided by Exchange22 provides his/her consents for receiving all the communications from Exchange22 by marking e-mails from Exchange22.com as part of their safe senders list. In an event, if any of the emails sent by Exchange22 remains unread by the User because of being sent to the Spam or Junk folders, Exchange22 shall not be held responsible.\n\n Any passwords issued by Exchange22 to any of the individual using the services provided by Exchange22 are confidential and should not be shared by the users with anyone else. The User holds the sole responsibility of maintaining the confidentiality of their accounts and passwords. The User offers his/her consent by agreeing to the Terms and Conditions of Exchange22 to inform Exchange22 about any unauthorized use of their passwords or accounts or any other breach of security.\n\n The User is solely responsible for the security and confidentiality of his/her payment accounts linked to his/her Exchange22 account. In case of any misuse of the linked payment accounts of the user, Exchange22 shall not be held liable; further, such misuse of the linked payment accounts of the user should be reported to Exchange22 as soon as it comes to the notice of the user.\n\n The User ensures to exit/log-out of their accounts after the completion of each session. In case of any sort of loss or damage faced by the user due to the failure of abiding these rules and regulations, Exchange22 shall not be held responsible.]]></string>
    <string name="term_ten_Description">The User using Services provided by Exchange22 should neither conduct nor assist the usage of cheats, exploits, automation, software, bots, hacks or any unauthorized third-party software specifically formulated for modifying or intervening with Exchange22.com and/or Exchange22 experience.\n\n The User using Services offered by Exchange22 Portal provides their consent of not copying, modifying the technology and software associated with Exchange22. Further, the User accepts not to rent, loan, sell, assign, distribute, reverse engineer, grant a security interest in, or otherwise transfer any right to anyone of the associated technologies and software.\n\n The Terms and Conditions of Exchange22 bounds the User to neither modify nor become a cause of modification of any of the files, technology or software associated with Exchange22.\n\n The User provides their acceptance to not disrupt, overburden, or promote any kind of disruption or overburdening to the servers or computers offering or supporting Exchange22 Services or the enjoyment of Exchange22.com Services by other User.\n\n The User shall neither support or conduct any sort of attack including (but not limited to) distribution of a virus or computer contaminants (as defined in the Information Technology Act, 2000 or such other laws in force in India at the relevant time) which may interrupt, destroy, limit the functionality or disrupt any software, hardware or other equipment belonging to us or that aids in providing the Services offered by Exchange22 or which shall restrict the use or enjoyment of other Exchange22 users.\n\n Any form of fraudulent activity including, attempting to use or using any other person\'s credit card(s), debit cards, net-banking usernames, passwords, authorization codes, prepaid cash cards, mobile phones for adding cash to your user account is strictly prohibited.\n\n Winnings, bonuses and prizes are unique to the player and are non-transferable. In the event you attempt to transfer any winnings, bonuses or prizes, these will be forfeited.\n\n The User shall not use Services on the Portal for commercial purposes including but not limited to use in a cyber cafe as a computer gaming centre, network play over the Internet or through gaming networks or connection to an unauthorized server that copies the gaming experience on the Website.\n\n The User provides their acceptance for not using the Exchange22 platform for any sort of inadequate activities including (but not limited to):\n\n \n\n\t\tTo engage in any obscene, offensive, indecent, racial, communal, anti-national, objectionable, defamatory or abusive action or communication; \n\t\tTo harass, stalk, threaten, or otherwise violate any legal rights of other individuals; \n\t\tTo advertise, offer or sell any goods or services for any commercial purpose on Exchange22.com without the express written consent of Exchange22; and\n\t\t To transmit content regarding services, products, surveys, contests, pyramid schemes, spam, unsolicited advertising or promotional materials, or chain letters. \n\nThe User shall not post any material or comment, on any media available for public access, which in our sole discretion, is defamatory or detrimental to our business interests, notwithstanding the fact that such media is not owned or controlled by us. In addition to any other action that we may take pursuant to the provision hereof, we reserve the right to remove any and all material or comments posted by you and restrict your access to any media available for public access that is either controlled or moderate by us; when in our sole opinion, any such material or comments posted by you is defamatory or detrimental to our business interests.11. User Account Suspension\n\n We may suspend or otherwise put restrictions on your access to the Services on the Websites during investigation for any of the following reasons:\n\n \n\t\tSuspected violation of Terms or other abuse of your user account; \n\t\tSuspected breach of security of your user account; or \n\t\tIf there have been charge-backs on your user account.\n\nOur decision to suspend or restrict Service or any part thereof as we deem appropriate shall be final and binding on you.</string>
    <string name="term_eleven_description">In case of any technical failures, server crashes, breakdowns, software defects, disruption or malfunction of service, as a policy, Hulm Entertainment Private Limited will cancel the Contest(s) and refund the amounts after proper verification and you accept that Hulm Entertainment Private Limitedis not responsible to you in all such cases. Hulm Entertainment Private Limited is also not liable for any prospective winnings from any incomplete tournament.\n\n It is clarified that, notwithstanding any limitation of liability as specified herein, Hulm Entertainment Private Limited specifically disclaims any liability in the case of Contest(s) where there is no money paid by you.\n\n You agree that under no circumstances shall you compel Hulm Entertainment Private Limited or hold Hulm Entertainment Private Limited liable to pay you any amount over and above the service charges for any of the aforementioned errors/omissions of Hulm Entertainment Private Limited.</string>
    <string name="term_trl_descripton"><![CDATA[The withdrawal request of a user is processed within 2-3 days (herein the working hours refers to bank’s working hours) excluding the date the request is made. In case, your withdrawal request is not processed within 2-3 days after the date the request is made; please check your registered email address provided by you at the time of registration for any communications from Exchange22.\n\n In an event, any Exchange22 user is found to be violating the Fair Play Terms, or in general Terms & Conditions of the Portal then Exchange22 at its sole and absolute discretion holds all the rights to take strict measures against the users.\n\n In an event a User is found to be having more than single Id registered on Exchange22 or multiple Ids registered under the same name then the withdrawal request of such users can either be put on hold, or their user accounts can be blocked refraining them from playing further on Exchange22.\n\n Any user if ever found to be violating the Fair Play Terms of Exchange22 which can be visited on Fair Play, will be either blocked from playing further on Exchange22 or his/her withdrawal requests will be put on hold for violating the Fair Play terms.\n\n The withdrawals of users found to be creating a fake refer chain by creating multiple ids under the same name to earn the Refer & Earn bonus will be blocked from using Exchange22 Services provided by the Portal alongside putting their withdrawal requests on hold.\n\n In an event, any user is identified to be a resident of Sikkim, Assam, Odisha, Telangana or Nagaland or Andhra Pradesh and Tamil Nadu amid the Exchange22 audits and had hidden this fact while registering at the platform will be blocked, and his/her withdrawal requests will be put on hold.\n\n Exchange22 could put the withdrawal requests of users violating the Fair Play terms of Exchange22 or can block the user account at any stage amid its audits, no matter if the withdrawal requests of the user had been accepted previously.\n\n In case the withdrawal request of a user is kept on hold, and Exchange22 at its sole & absolute discretion decides to process the withdrawal request of that user after he/she agrees to abide by the Fair Play Terms of Exchange22 then such withdrawals shall take 5-7 working days to process.\n\n In case, we suspect any account to be violating our fair play or verification terms already stated in the Terms & Conditions of Exchange22; we hold all the rights to verify the user at any time. Exchange22 holds all the rights to video call any user at any point of time to validate & verify his/her identity. If the video call done as a part of the verification process is found to be negative, then the user account shall be blocked &his withdrawal shall be put on hold. Exchange22 is free by all means to verify & validate the identity of a user at any point of time as per its will/wish.\n\n In case, a user is using a single device for creating multiple accounts on Exchange22, it should be ensured by the user that all the mandatory verification formalities including mobile, email, PAN card & Bank Account details verification has been done by the user for all the accounts created. Abiding by the said process will help such users, who create multiple accounts on a single device, in terms of smooth withdrawals on Exchange22.]]></string>
    <string name="term_thr_description">Exchange22 is neither affiliated by nor associated with any private or government Sports leagues and tournaments, until and unless expressly stated by the Company. In addition to this, Exchange22 is not related and does not claim any official status with any of the official or non-official sports team or sportsperson.\n\n The Services on the Portal and the content present on it are provided strictly on basis with all faults or failings. Any representations, warranties, conditions or guarantee whatsoever, express or implied (including, without limitation, any implied warranty of accuracy, completeness, uninterrupted provision, quality, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement) are specifically excluded to the fullest extent permitted by law.\n\nTo the extent permitted under law, neither Exchange22 nor its parent/holding company, subsidiaries, affiliates, directors, officers, professional advisors, employees shall be responsible for the deletion, the failure to store, the mis-delivery, or the untimely delivery of any information or material.\n\nIn alignment to the legal bodies, Exchange22 shall not be held responsible for any harm faced due to downloading or accessing any information or material, the quality of servers, games, products or sites, cancellation of competition and prizes. Exchange22 does not hold any responsibility if a User pays for access to one of Exchange22\'s Services and the User shall not be provided any refund as a result of, any inaccessibility that is caused by Exchange22\'s maintenance on the servers or the technology that underlies our sites, failures of Exchange22\'s service providers (including telecommunications, hosting, and power providers), computer viruses, natural disasters or other destruction or damage of our facilities, acts of nature, war, civil disturbance, or any other cause beyond our reasonable control.\n\nThe User is solely responsible for any sort of material accessed, downloaded or otherwise obtained through Exchange22.com and holds the sole responsibility for any potential damage to their computer system or loss of data that occurs as a result of downloading or accessing any such material.\n\nExchange22 shall make best endeavours to ensure that the Exchange22 Portal is error-free and secure; however, neither Exchange22 nor any of its partners, licensors or associates makes any warranty that:\n\nthe Exchange22.com Portal will meet Users’ requirements; \n\t\tExchange22.com(s) Portal will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error-free; \n\nthe results that may be obtained from the use of Exchange22.com Portal will be accurate or reliable; and \n\nthe quality of any products, Services, information, or other material that Users purchase or obtain through Exchange22.com Portal will meet Users’ expectations. \n\nExchange22 holds all the rights to rectify any errors identified in the determination of winnings or in the transfer of amounts to a User\'s account, using various method as it deems fit, including (but not limited to) through a set-off of the mistaken payment from amounts due to the User or deduction from the User\'s account of the amount of mistaken payment. In such events, Exchange22 agrees to notify the user about the error and the rectification measure adopted to address the error. \n\nComplying to the legal bodies and authorities neither Exchange22 nor its partners, licensors or associates disclaims any sort of responsibility for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising out of the use of or inability to use our sites, even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damages. \n\nExchange22 is authorized to cancel any Services, events or Contest(s) requiring specific permission or authority from any statutory authority or any state or the central government, or the board of directors in an event wherein such permission or authority is either not obtained or denied either before or after the organization of the relevant events or Contest(s). \n\nBy accepting these Terms and Conditions, the users agree not to make any demands, or claims in the event of suspension or closure of any Services, events or Contests organized/provided by Exchange22.</string>
    <string name="withdraw_one_title">How do I withdraw cash?</string>
    <string name="withdraw_two_title">Can I use someone else\'s bank account to withdraw money?</string>
    <string name="withdraw_three_title">When will my withdrawal be processed?</string>
    <string name="withdraw_one_Description">You can Withdraw Cash at any time by following the below mentioned steps: \n\nStep 1: Login to your Exchange22 account on the App.\n\nStep 2: Visit the ‘My Balance’ page and click on ‘Cash Withdraw’ option under the winnings section. \n\nStep 3: Enter an amount you would like to withdraw. However, you can only withdraw an amount less than or equal to your Balance that can be withdrawn. This will be shown to you on the Withdraw Cash page. \n\nFor making a withdrawal, your account has to be ID verified. Your PAN Card and Bank Ac-count details (Your Name, Name of the Bank, Account Number, IFS Code and Branch Name) has to be verified before placing a withdrawal request. In case you have not verified your account, you shall be prompted to upload your PAN Card details and Bank Account details following which our customer service executives will review and verify your uploaded document. You can also get yourself ID verified by uploading ID proof document from the ‘Verify Account’ section in the App. \n\nWhat is the minimum amount that can be withdrawn? \n\nA minimum amount of ₹200 can be withdrawn once per 24 hours.\n\nWhat is the maximum amount that can be withdrawn?\n\nA maximum amount of ₹50,000 can be withdrawn once per 24 hours.If you wish to withdraw more than ₹50,000 once per 24 hours, please get in touch with our support team on Facebook Messenger or write to us at contact@exchange22.com.\n\nIs there any charge on withdrawal of amount? \n\nNo, we do not charge any amount on withdrawal. \n\n However, in normal buy/sell trade, we charge 6% per trade initiated by you. Also, for with-drawal on multi-bagger trades, we charge 20% of the pooled money as portal charges and distribute the remaining 80% amongst the winner(s). \n\nThe charges help us improve and provide you with better interface so that you can enjoy and experience the thrill better.</string>
    <string name="withdraw_two_description">Unfortunately, you can withdraw money from your Exchange22 account balance ONLY to your own bank account. If you do not have a bank account, your winnings will keep getting accumulated in your Exchange22 account balance. Once you get a bank account in your name, you can use the same to get your Exchange22 account verified and place your with-drawal requests.</string>
    <string name="withdraw_three_description">In cases of Instant Withdrawal Process (via IMPS) method of transfer the withdrawal might take 2-3 hours for the amount to reflect in your bank account. In case of delay on the part of the Bank to credit the funds to your account, it may take up to 3 working days. \n\nNormally, withdrawals are processed on the next working day of submitting a withdrawal request and are transferred to your verified bank account within 5 working days. Remember, your Exchange22 account must be completely verified before you place a withdrawal re-quest. \n\nWe process Online Transfers on all days except Sunday and Bank Holidays. \n\nWhen can my withdrawal be cancelled? \n\n Your withdrawal may have been cancelled in the system due to one of the below reasons: \n\nIncorrect IFS code verified on the account \n\nName on the bank does not match with the name verified on Exchange22 account \n\nIncorrect account number verified on the account \n\n In case your withdrawal has been cancelled due to the above reason, be rest assured that your amount will be credited back to your Exchange22 account and you will be asked to verify the correct bank details to place another withdrawal request. You can go ahead and complete your verification again and withdraw the winnings to the correct bank account. \n\n Further, If you\'ve verified a bank account that belongs to Telangana, Assam or Odisha , Nagaland and Andhra Pradesh, Sikkim and Tamil Nadu, your withdrawal will be rejected. If you are based outside the states mentioned above, kindly place a verification request of a bank account that isn\'t located in any of them. \n\n Also, Exchange22 shall not be liable for any loss of any amount due to an incorrect but valid account number verified on the portal. \n\n In case of violation of the ‘Fair Play Terms’ of Exchange22, the withdrawal request will be put on hold until resolution. \n\n Disclaimers :\n\nExchange22, may, at its sole and absolute discretion, can hold or deactivate the Instant Withdrawal service anytime without any prior information to the user.\n\nIn case of a dispute, disagreement or concern between Exchange22 and its payment partner, Exchange22 holds all the right to put the withdrawal requests and amounts on hold till such dispute is resolved.</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How to play</string>
    <string name="feature_s">Feature\'s</string>
    <string name="legality">Legality</string>
    <string name="withdraw_terms">Withdraw Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_amp_condition"><![CDATA[Terms & Condition]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="about_app">About</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="fb_banner">IMG_16_9_APP_INSTALL#YOUR_PLACEMENT_ID</string>
    <string name="fb_interstrial">IMG_16_9_APP_INSTALL#YOUR_PLACEMENT_ID</string>
</resources>